sendwithus.com 2016-06-02

# Privacy Policy · sendwithus

##### Last Updated: February 13, 2015

Thanks for using Sendwithus, and taking the time to read through this =]

Sendwithus is owned and operated by Techdrop Labs Inc. ("Techdrop Labs").  
Techdrop Labs is committed to protecting the privacy of your information.

  * #### Web Site Covered

This Privacy Policy covers the information practices of [sendwithus.com](http://sendwithus.com/).

  * #### Information Collected

Techdrop Labs offers a service under of the name sendwithus (the "Service"). Techdrop Labs collects information from individuals who visit the Company’s Web site (“Visitors”) and individuals who register to use the Service (“Customers”).

    * When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Service or registering to use the Service, Techdrop Labs requires you to provide personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address (“Required Contact Information”).

    * When purchasing the Service, Techdrop Labs requires you to provide the Company with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, and credit card number (“Billing Information”).

    * Techdrop Labs may also ask you to provide additional information, such as industry, company revenues, or number of employees (“Optional Information”).

Required Contact Information, Billing Information, and Optional Information are referred to collectively as “Data About Techdrop Labs Customers.”

    * As you navigate the Company’s Web site, Techdrop Labs may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons (“Web Site Navigational Information”). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Company’s Web site (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).

  * #### Use of Information Collected

The Company uses Data About Techdrop Labs Customers to perform the services requested.

    * For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” Web form, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Services.

    * Techdrop Labs uses Contact Information for account access, service notifications, and other purposes related to use of the Services.

    * Techdrop Labs uses credit card information solely to check the financial qualifications of prospective Customers and to collect payment for the Services.

    * The Company may also use Data About Techdrop Labs Customers for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

    * Techdrop Labs uses Web Site Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s Web site. The Company may also use Web Site Navigational Information alone or in combination with Data About Techdrop Labs Customers to provide personalized information about the Company.

  * ##### Web Site Navigational Information

Techdrop Labs uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the Company’s Web site (“Web Site Navigational Information”). This section describes the types of Web Site Navigational Information that may be collected on the Company’s Web site and how this information may be used.

    1. #### Cookies

Techdrop Labs uses cookies to make interactions with the Company’s Web site easy and meaningful. When you visit the Company’s Web site, Techdrop Labs servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you. They merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to Techdrop Labs, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a Web form (such as a “Contact Me” or other Web forms that may be displayed), you remain anonymous to the Company. Techdrop Labs uses cookies that are session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.

If you have chosen to identify yourself to Techdrop Labs, the Company uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the Company to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the Services, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed your browser. These session cookies allow the Company to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Services and to process your online transactions and r equests. Session cookies are required to use the Services.

Techdrop Labs uses persistent cookies that only the Company can read and use to identify browsers that have previously visited the Company’s Web site. When you purchase the Services or provide the Company with personal information, a unique identifier is assigned you. This unique identifier is associated with a persistent cookie that the Company places on your Web browser. The Company is especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, the Company does not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. If you disable your Web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate the Company’s Web site, but you will not be able to successfully use the Services.

Techdrop Labs may use information from session and persistent cookies in combination with Data About Techdrop Labs Customers to provide you with information about the Company and the Services.

    2. #### Web Beacons

Techdrop Labs uses Web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about Customers and Visitors’ usage of the Company’s Web site and interaction with emails from the Company. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Web site tied to the Web beacon, and a description of a Web site tied to the Web beacon. For example, Techdrop Labs may place Web beacons in marketing emails that notify the Company when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of the Company’s Web site. Techdrop Labs uses Web beacons to operate and improve the Company’s Web site and email communications.

Techdrop Labs may use information from Web beacons in combination with Data About Techdrop Labs Customers to provide you with information about the Company and the Services.

    3. #### IP Addresses

When you visit Techdrop Labs' Web site, the Company collects your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses to track and aggregate non-personal information. For example, Techdrop Labs uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company’s Web site.

    4. #### Third Party Cookies

From time-to-time, Techdrop Labs engages third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit the Company’s Web site. Techdrop Labs may also use other third-party cookies to track the performance of Company advertisements. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after the Company receives it.

Techdrop Labs may also contract with third-party advertising networks that collect IP addresses and other Web Site Navigational Information on the Company’s Web site and emails and on third-party Web sites. Ad networks follow your online activities over time by collecting Web Site Navigational Information through automated means, including through the use of cookies. They use this information to provide advertisements about products and services tailored to your interests. You may see these advertisements on other Web sites. This process also helps us manage and track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

  * #### Public Forums, Refer a Friend, and Customer Testimonials

Techdrop Labs may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on the Company’s Web site directly or via third-party services. Any personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. Techdrop Labs is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.

Techdrop Labs may post a list of Customers and testimonials on the Company’s Web site that contain information such as Customer names and titles. Techdrop Labs obtains the consent of each Customer prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials.

  * #### Sharing of Information Collected

Techdrop Labs may share Data About Techdrop Labs Customers with the Company’s service providers so that these service providers can contact Customers and Visitors who have provided contact information on our behalf. Techdrop Labs may also share Data About Techdrop Labs Customers with the Company’s service providers to ensure the quality of information provided. Unless described in this privacy statement, Techdrop Labs does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information provided with third parties for their promotional purposes.

From time to time, Techdrop Labs may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. If you purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly-offered product or service from Techdrop Labs, the Company may share Data About Techdrop Labs Customers collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our joint promotion partner(s). Techdrop Labs does not control our business partners’ use of the Data About Techdrop Labs Customers we collect, and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service.

Techdrop Labs uses a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company’s behalf.

Techdrop Labs reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if the Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

  * #### International Data Collection and Transfer

The Company’s Web site and Services are hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Web site and/or Services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions. By providing your personal data you consent to:

    * The use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and

    * The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

To facilitate Techdrop Labs global operations, the Company may transfer and access Data About Techdrop Labs Customers from around the world, including the United States. This Privacy Statement shall apply even if Techdrop Labs transfers Data About Techdrop Labs Customers to other countries.

  * #### European Union Data Protection

To the extent that we store data in the United States, we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries.

If you reside in the European Union, upon registration for any applicable Techdrop Labs service or offering you consent that the personal information you have provided may be transferred and stored in countries outside the EU.

To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

  * #### Communications Preferences

Techdrop Labs offers Customers and Visitors who provide contact information a means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the Company’s marketing emails. Additionally, you may send a request specifying your communications preferences to [support@sendwithus.com](mailto:support@sendwithus.com). Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with Techdrop Labs or the Services.

  * #### Correcting and Updating Your Information

Customers may update or change their registration information by logging in to their accounts at <https://app.sendwithus.com/login>. Requests to Techdrop Labs to modify or delete your information will be handled within 30 days once customer account ownership has been verified.

  * #### Security

Techdrop Labs uses appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect Data About Techdrop Labs Customers.

  * #### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Techdrop Labs reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. Techdrop Labs will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through the Company’s Web Site at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.

  * #### Contacting Us

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of the Company’s Web site should be directed to [legal@sendwithus.com](mailto:legal@sendwithus.com) or by mailing

Techdrop Labs Inc. Legal  
375 Water Street  
Suite 680  
Vancouver, BC V6B 5C6  
Canada

Congratulations, you made it all the way to the bottom!

Enjoy a cupcake, on the house!
